Paige Reynolds

pkreynol@syr.edu

(607) 591-9707

3505 Broadway Apartment 63 New York, NY 10031

Dear Hiring Manager:

I am a recent Master's graduate in both Special Education Grades 1-6 and Elementary

Education Grades 1-6 from Syracuse University, with NYS certification in both. I hope that I

will be considered for a special education instructor position with Tutors on Wheels.

I have experience teaching and supporting diverse students, with and without disabilities.

Throughout my student teaching field placements, I have taught in inclusive classrooms and

special education classrooms. I have taught as a co-teacher, a general education classroom

teacher, a consultant teacher, and a resource teacher. I also have experience tutoring and

giving extra support to individuals and small groups.

I have designed curriculum and assessment tools, and have used assessment data

effectively to guide instruction. I have administered standardized measures of assessment

to identify students with disabilities and designed interventions to target students' needs. I

have worked as part of a team designing and implementing IEPs and have participated in

CSE meetings as well as parent-teacher conferences. I believe that my experiences have

given me the advantage of a strong understanding of the relationship between assessment

and instruction.

I strongly believe in my ability to effectively support all learners across all settings. I believe

I would be a valuable member of the Tutors on Wheels team.

Thank you for your consideration,

Paige Reynolds

Paige Reynolds

pkreynol@syr.edu

(607) 591-9707

3505 Broadway Apartment 63 New York, NY 10031

EDUCATION

Syracuse University

Master of Science in Elementary Education (1-6), 3.98 GPA Master of Science in Inclusive Special Education (1-6), 3.98 GPA

Spring 2013 Fall 2013

University at Albany State University of New York

Bachelor of Arts in Psychology, 3.8 GPA

May 2012

CERTIFICATIONS

New York State Certification 1-6 Students with Disabilities New York State Certification 1-6 General Education February 2014

FIELD PLACEMENTS

Student Teacher- Special Education (1st & 5th Grade)

Fall 2013

Elden Elementary School, Baldwinsville Central School District

- Served as a Consultant Special Ed Teacher, Co-Teacher, and Resource Teacher
- Attended and gave input at CSE Meetings

Psychoeducational Teaching Laboratory

Summer 2013

Syracuse University

· Administered standardized measures of assessment, evaluated students and gave interventions

Student Teacher- Inclusive Classroom (6th grade)

Spring 2013

Ed Smith K-8 School, Syracuse City School District

- Served as an Inclusive teacher of three 6th grade classes
- Provided supports for 38 students with a range of disabilities to access the general classroom

Student Teacher- Inclusive Classroom (3rd grade)

Spring 2013

Fremont Elementary School, East Syracuse Minoa Central School District

• Taught all content areas, collaboratively designed and implemented behavior plans

Professional Practicum- Inclusive Classrooms (2nd grade)

Fall/Winter 2012

Delaware Academy, Syracuse City School District

- Taught lessons in the content areas
- Administered reading and math interventions to small groups and tracked progress

EMPLOYMENT

Daycare Center, Family Counseling Services of Cortland (Cortland, NY) Colonie Youth Center Before and After School Program (Albany, NY) Virgil Summer Vacation Camp (Cortland, NY) 2013 2011-2012 School Year Counselor 2007-2012

ACTIVITIES

Middle Earth Crisis Hotline, University at Albany
Co-author of published children's book & blog on inclusive education
http://entriesthroughdiverseeyes.wordpress.com

Hotline Counselor 2010-2012

2013